So now let's try to use some of these phrases in a real situation and I'm going to try to make it as
所以现在让我们尝试在实际情况中使用其中一些短语，我将尝试将其设为
realistic as possible.
尽可能现实。
Let's say for example you move to America OK or let's say you already live here and you want to move
例如，假设您搬到美国可以，或者假设您已经住在这里并且想搬家
to another place.
到另一个地方。
I use America because I'm American so I know kind of how it works.
我使用美国是因为我是美国人，所以我知道它是如何运作的。
I've had many apartments before.
我以前有很多公寓。
An apartment is a place people live in a larger building usually it's not a stand alone building a standalone
公寓是人们居住在较大建筑物中的地方，通常它不是独立的，而是独立的
building is probably called a house and maybe only one family lives there.
建筑可能被称为房子，也许只有一个家庭住在那里。
An apartment is usually in a larger building and it's usually smaller.
公寓通常位于较大的建筑物中，并且通常较小。
OK so we're gonna do an apartment inquiry or inquiry and we're gonna be calling the landlord can also
好的，所以我们要进行公寓查询或查询，我们要打电话给房东也可以
say landlady.
说女房东。
Now this is the owner of the apartment.
现在这是公寓的主人。
The owner of the apartment.
公寓的主人。
If it's not the owner then it's probably a broker or agent in America.
如果不是所有者，那么它可能是美国的经纪人或代理人。
And for example in New York an agent will take a fee and I guess that's probably true anywhere in the
例如在纽约，代理人会收取费用，我想这可能在纽约的任何地方都是如此
world.
世界。
So if you go through an agent you probably need to pay more if you can call the landlord or landlady
因此，如果您通过代理，如果您可以致电房东或女房东，您可能需要支付更多费用
or owner directly that's usually better in this situation we're going to actually call the WE'RE GONNA
或直接所有者，在这种情况下通常会更好，我们将实际调用 WE'RE GONNA
GET THE NUMBER OF THE LANDLORD AND WE'RE GONNA CALL and we're gonna get some information because we're
得到房东的电话号码，我们会打电话，我们会得到一些信息，因为我们是
interested in the apartment.
对公寓感兴趣。
Now there are many ways to find an apartment in America.
现在有很多方法可以在美国找到公寓。
There are a lot of Web sites you can you can of course go to an agency you can look in the maybe the
有很多网站，你当然可以去一个代理机构，你可以看看
newspaper but there are some popular web web sites that you can use like Craigslist dot com.
报纸，但您可以使用一些流行的网站，例如 Craigslist dot com。
And there are some other ones like Zillow dot com.
还有一些其他的，比如 Zillow dot com。
And who knows maybe when you're watching this it's 50 years from now for when this is being filmed and
谁知道当你在看这个的时候，从现在开始已经是 50 年了。
there's a completely different way of doing this but we use generally a Web site then we'll find a a
有一种完全不同的方法，但我们通常使用一个网站，然后我们会找到一个
listing find a listing listing is basically a post that someone has put up on one of these Web sites
列表 查找列表 列表基本上是某人在其中一个网站上发布的帖子
and we usually search based on some certain criteria.
我们通常根据某些特定条件进行搜索。
We have some criteria.
我们有一些标准。
This is what we're searching.
这就是我们正在寻找的。
Maybe I'm looking for a one bedroom and this is often abbreviated as B R one bedroom one bathroom.
也许我正在寻找一间卧室，这通常缩写为 B R 一卧室一浴室。
So if you see one B are one B R that means one bedroom one bathroom bedroom is usually first.
因此，如果您看到一个 B 是一个 B R，这意味着一间卧室通常是一间浴室卧室。
So if you see to be are one bra that means two bedrooms one bathroom if you see to be are too bizarre
因此，如果您认为是一件胸罩，这意味着两间卧室，一间浴室，如果您认为是太奇怪了
it means two bedrooms two bathrooms you get the idea.
这意味着两间卧室两间浴室你明白的。
You'll also often see how many square feet in America we usually use feet feet to measure.
您还会经常看到在美国我们通常使用英尺来测量多少平方英尺。
So it'll say often F T R S Q F T like that square feet square feet.
所以它会经常说 F T R S Q F T 就像那个平方英尺。
If you're in another country then maybe it's square meter square meter.
如果您在另一个国家/地区，那么可能是平方米平方米。
Right.
正确的。
And then of course you'll see the asking price asking price or the price per month the rent.
然后当然你会看到要价要价或每月租金的价格。
We often call this just the rent and let's say it's 1000 let's say we're looking for something that's
我们经常称这只是租金，假设它是 1000，假设我们正在寻找的东西
one thousand five hundred dollars.
一千五百美元。
OK one thousand five hundred dollars.
好的一千五百美元。
The poster or the listing will also have probably the neighborhood.
海报或列表也可能有邻居。
So let's say it's in Brooklyn.
假设它在布鲁克林。
Brooklyn isn't a neighborhood.
布鲁克林不是一个街区。
Brooklyn is a burrow in New York.
布鲁克林是纽约的一个洞穴。
Let's say the neighborhood is Greenpoint.
假设附近是 Greenpoint。
OK.
好的。
So we see a post we see a listing.
所以我们看到一个帖子，我们看到一个列表。
It says one bedroom one B R one B R and it's a one bedroom one bathroom it's in Greenpoint.
上面写着一卧室一卧室一卧室一卧室一卧室一浴室它在Greenpoint。
And the rent is one thousand five hundred which maybe is too expensive.
而且租金是一千五百，可能太贵了。52
We think it's too much.
我们认为这太过分了。
Actually that's pretty cheap.
其实这很便宜。
One thousand five hundred for Greenpoint.
Greenpoint 一千五百。
That's pretty cheap and maybe there are some extra details here.
这很便宜，也许这里有一些额外的细节。
Let's say it says its newly renovated.
假设它说它是新装修的。
That means there was some old things and those things were taken out and maybe there's a new kitchen.
这意味着有一些旧东西被拿出来，也许还有一个新厨房。
They completely redid the apartment and maybe it also says it's fully furnished now furnished or unfurnished
他们完全重新装修了公寓，也许它还说它现在家具齐全或不带家具
furnished means that there's a sofa there's a bed.
家具意味着有沙发有床。
All of that stuff is already there unfurnished means there's nothing except for appliances appliances
所有这些东西都已经在那里没有家具意味着除了电器之外什么都没有
are maybe the microwave the sometimes the TV dishwasher the oven perhaps these are air conditioning.
也许是微波炉，有时是电视洗碗机，烤箱，也许这些是空调。
These are appliances furnishings are bed sofa tables chairs that sort of thing.
这些是家电家具是床沙发桌子椅子之类的东西。
So let's say it's fairly full before it's fully furnished and newly renovated.
因此，假设它在设备齐全和新装修之前已经相当满了。
And these are the other details here and there's a phone number.
这些是这里的其他详细信息，还有一个电话号码。
Hey so we're gonna call the phone number and we're going to talk directly to the land lord.
嘿，所以我们要拨打电话号码，我们要直接与房东交谈。